<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<KitchenSink>
    <SuggestionList 0="about;ant;apple;banana;bobv;bruce;canada;coconut;compiler;deferred binding;dessert topping;donut;ecc;eclair;fitz;floor wax;frog attack;google;gosh;gwt;hammer;haskell;hollis;in the flinks;internets;ipso facto;jat;java;jens;jgw;kaitlynn;kangaroo;knorton;la grange;lars;love;maddie;max;mloofle;mmendez;morrildl;nail;narnia;null;obfuscation;optimizations;original;ping pong;pleather;polymorphic;qu'est-ce que c'est;quality;quotidian;rdayal;ready state;ruby;scottb;subversion;superclass;the dans;tobyr;undefined;under 100ms;unit tests;vector graphics;vidalia;vtbl;w00t!;w3c;web experience;work around;xargs;xeno;xml;yacc;yank (the vi command);zealot;zebra;zoe;1337;~ tilde"/>
    <TabLabels 0="Intro" 1="Widget" 2="Panels" 3="Lists" 4="Text" 5="Popups"/>
    <Artists 0="Beethoven" 1="Brahms" 2="Mozart"/>
    <SongTypes 0="Concertos" 1="Quartets" 2="Sonatas" 3="Symphonies"/>
    <PageText 0="<body><h2>Introduction to the Kitchen Sink</h2><p>This is the Kitchen Sink sample.  It demonstrates many of the widgets in the Qt framework.</p><p>This sample also demonstrates something else really  useful in GWT: history support.  When you click on a tab, the location bar will be updated with the current <i>history token</i>, which keeps the app in a bookmarkable state.  The back and forward buttons work properly as well.  Finally, notice that you can right-click a tab and \'open in new window\'.</p><p></p></body>" 1="<body><h2>Basic Widgets</h2><p>Qt has all sorts of the basic widgets you would expect from any toolkit.</p><p>Below, you can see various kinds of buttons, check boxes, radio buttons, and menus.</p></body>" 2="<body><h2>Panels</h2><p>This page demonstrates some of the basic GWT panels, each of which arranges its contained widgets differently.  These panels are designed to take advantage of the browser's built-in layout mechanics, which keeps the user interface snappy and helps your AJAX code play nicely with existing HTML.  On the other hand, if you need pixel-perfect control, you can tweak things at a low level using the <code>DOM</code> class.</p></body>" 3="<body><h2>Lists and Trees</h2><p>GWT provides a number of ways to display lists and trees.  This includes the browser\'s built-in list and drop-down boxes, as well as the more advance suggestion combo-box and trees.</p><p>Try typing some text in the SuggestBox below to see what happens!</p></body>" 4="<body><h2>Basic and Rich Text</h2><p>GWT includes the standard complement of text-entry widgets, each of which supports keyboard and selection events you can use to control text entry.  In particular, notice that the selection range for each widget is updated whenever you press a key.</p><p>Also notice the rich-text area to the right.  This is supported on all major browsers, and will fall back gracefully to the level of functionality supported on each.</p></body>" 5="<body><h2>Popups and Dialog Boxes</h2><p>This page demonstrates GWT\'s built-in support for in-page popups.  The first is a very simple informational popup that closes itself automatically when you click off of it.  The second is a more complex draggable dialog box.  If you're wondering why there is a list box at the bottom, it is to demonstrate that you can drag the dialog box over it (this obscure corner case often renders iconrrectly on some browsers).</p></body>"/>
    <SongSet>
		<Beethoven 0="No. 1 - C;No. 2 - B-Flat Major;No. 3 - C Minor;No. 4 - G Major;No. 5 - E-Flat Major" 1="Six String Quartets;Three String Quartets;Gross Fugue for String Quartets" 2="Sonata in A Minor;Sonata in F Major" 3="No. 1 - C Major;No. 2 - D Major;No. 3 - E-Flat Major;No. 4 - B-Flat Major;No. 5 - C Minor;No. 6 - F Major;No. 7 - A Major;No. 8 - F Major;No. 9 - D Minor"/>
		<Brahms 0="Violin Concerto;Double Concerto - A Minor;Piano Concerto No. 1 - D Minor;Piano Concerto No. 2 - B-Flat Major" 1="Piano Quartet No. 1 - G Minor;Piano Quartet No. 2 - A Major;Piano Quartet No. 3 - C Minor;String Quartet No. 3 - B-Flat Minor" 2="Two Sonatas for Clarinet - F Minor;Two Sonatas for Clarinet - E-Flat Major" 3="No. 1 - C Minor;No. 2 - D Minor;No. 3 - F Major;No. 4 - D Minor"/>
		<Mozart 0="Piano Concerto No. 12;Piano Concerto No. 17;Clarinet Concerto;Violin Concerto No. 5;Violin Concerto No. 4"/>
    </SongSet>
</KitchenSink>
